{
    "subject": "resource/Lompoc,_California",
    "predicate": "http://xmlns.com/foaf/0.1/name",
    "object": "City of Lompoc",
    "human_readable": "The name of Lompoc, California is City of Lompoc.",
    "questions": [
        {
            "score": 0.9678667783737183,
            "question": "What is the official name of Lompoc, California?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.9575987458229065,
            "question": "Is Lompoc, California known by a different name?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.9532843828201294,
            "question": "What name is used to officially refer to Lompoc, California?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.9260034561157227,
            "question": "Besides 'Lompoc', what other name is given to this Californian city?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.8907697796821594,
            "question": "What nickname or title does Lompoc, California have?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.8834767937660217,
            "question": "What is the official designation for the city of Lompoc?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.8775385618209839,
            "question": "What title is given to Lompoc, California?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.8417370319366455,
            "question": "How is Lompoc, California officially identified?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.7922666668891907,
            "question": "What descriptive term is used for Lompoc, California?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.733863115310669,
            "question": "What phrase describes Lompoc, California's identity?"
        }
    ],
    "google_pages": [
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=The name of Lompoc, California is City of Lompoc.",
            "html": "dbpedia_3843_0.html"
        },
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=What descriptive term is used for Lompoc, California?",
            "html": "dbpedia_3843_1.html"
        },
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=How is Lompoc, California officially identified?",
            "html": "dbpedia_3843_2.html"
        },
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=What title is given to Lompoc, California?",
            "html": "dbpedia_3843_3.html"
        }
    ],
    "selected_docs": [
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_3843_14.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_3843_17.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_3843_19.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_3843_27.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_3843_3.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_3843_39.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_3843_42.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_3843_49.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_3843_79.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_3843_81.txt"
        }
    ],
    "final_question": "Is true?",
    "responses": {
        "gemma2": {
            "short_ans": 0,
            "full_ans": "```json\n{'output': 'no'}\n```  \n"
        },
        "llama3.1": {
            "short_ans": 0,
            "full_ans": "Here's the structured JSON format answer:\n\n```\n{\n  \"output\": \"no\"\n}\n```\n\nExplanation:\nThe query asks if the name of Lompoc, California is indeed \"City of Lompoc\". However, according to the provided context information (files), the city is referred to as \"Lompoc\" with various other names and descriptions such as \"Valley of Flowers\", but not specifically as \"City of Lompoc\". Therefore, based on this information, the query's statement does not hold true."
        },
        "qwen2.5": {
            "short_ans": 0,
            "full_ans": "```json\n{\n  \"output\": \"no\"\n}\n```\n\nExplanation: The documents provide information about the city of Lompoc, California, including its history and characteristics, but none of them state or imply that Lompoc is known as \"City of Lompoc.\" There are references to it being called \"Valley of Flowers\" in some documents."
        },
        "mistral": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": " {\"output\": \"yes\"}"
        }
    },
    "need_tiebreaker": false,
    "tiebreakers_responses": {
        "qwen2.5:14b": {},
        "llama3.1:70b": {}
    },
    "final_decision": 0,
    "actual_decision": 1,
    "analysis": {
        "stratum": "Less Popular",
        "topic": "-"
    },
    "errors": {
        "gemma2": {
            "reason": "Multiple sources clearly state the name of Lompoc is derived from a Purisime\u00f1o term, \"Lum Poc,\" meaning \"stagnant waters\" or \"lagoon.\"",
            "category": 2
        },
        "llama3.1": {
            "reason": "The context information provides multiple names for Lompoc, including \"City of Flowers\" (4), but not \"City of Lompoc\".",
            "category": 2
        },
        "qwen2.5": {
            "reason": "The name of Lompoc, California, as mentioned in the context, is derived from a Purisime\u00f1o term \"Lum Poc\", which means \"stagnant waters\" or \"lagoon\". There is no mention of it being called \"City of Lompoc.\"",
            "category": 2
        }
    }
}